#### Contact

kennang@me.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kennanbrown-55a98347 (LinkedIn) www.adventhealth.com (Other)

Top Skills
ACLS
Acute Care
Nursing

Certifications
Critical Care Registered Nurse

# Kennan Brown

BSN, RN, CCRN

Shawnee, Kansas

### Summary

Experienced Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Medicine, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Acute Care, and Computerized Physician Order Entry (CPOE). Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelors of Science in Nursing from Medcenter One College of Nursing. Nominated for 2018 and 2019 March of Dimes Critical Care Nurse of the Year in Kansas City. 2019 finalist for March of Dimes Critical Care Nurse of the Year. Participates in shared leadership for our Donate Life committee.

## Experience

AdventHealth Kansas City
Registered Nurse ICU
March 2014 - Present (6 years 5 months)
Shawnee Mission, Kansas

Shawnee Mission Health
Registered Nurse ER
July 2008 - March 2014 (5 years 9 months)
Shawnee Mission, Kansas

Sanford Health Registered Nurse ER June 2007 - July 2008 (1 year 2 months) Fargo, North Dakota

**Emergency Room** 

#### Education

Medcenter One College of Nursing

Bachelors of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2005 - 2007)

North Dakota State University
Undergraduate courses, Nursing · (2003 - 2005)